MURILO FLORIANI

Software Engineer

DETAILS

PHONE

+55 47 99106 3163

EMAIL

murilo.floriani@gmail.com

LINKS

Portfolio

<u>Github</u>

Linkedin

SKILLS

Video Game Development

C++

Unreal Engine

Computer Graphics

3D Math

Web Development

JavaScript

C#

LANGUAGES

English

Portuguese

PROFILE

I'm an experienced **Software Engineer**, who started my career designing and implementing multiple IT solutions, then shifted over to the gaming industry after completing a master's degree in Computer Science in Games Development at the University of Hull in the UK.

The MSc experience deepened my understanding of cutting-edge technologies in the gaming industry and culminated in working professionally on games for over 3 years where 2 of those years in a UK-based studio on an unannounced AAA arcade racing game in Unreal Engine 5 for a major publisher.

WORK HISTORY

Indie Game Developer

Brazil

Aug 2023 — Present

I am working on an unannounced indie game (Rust meets This War of Mine) in Unreal Engine 5.

Keywords: Unreal Engine 5; C++; Gameplay; Systems;

Associate Software Engineer, Stellar Entertainment

Guildford - UK

Sep 2021 — Jul 2023

I worked on an unannounced AAA arcade racing game for a major publisher in Unreal Engine 5, mostly related to gameplay and multiplayer code.

Keywords: Unreal Engine 5; C++; Gameplay; Multiplayer; Perforce;

Software Developer, Jaguar Land Rover

Shannon - Ireland

Feb 2019 — Jul 2020

I worked in the R&D team responsible for developing a back-end solution to process payment requests from the vehicles' infotainment system.

Keywords: NodeJs; RabbitMQ; Docker;

Software Developer, Indielogic Studios

Brazil

Oct 2014 — Jan 2018

I designed and implemented ERP solutions for a manufacturing company.

Keywords: Oracle Stack; C#; Asp.Net;

Software Developer, Gessis

Brazil

Feb 2013 — Sep 2014

Designed and implemented features for our in-house web platform focused on extending the client's ERP system limitations.

Keywords: PHP; C#;

Software Developer

Brazil

Jun 2006 — Jan 2013

Designed and implemented multiple on-demand features for multiple clients as a contractor.

Keywords: Oracle stack; C#; SQL;

EDUCATION

MSc in Computer Science for Games Development, University of Hull

Hull - UK

Sep 2020 — Jan 2022

Post-Graduate in Games Development,

Brazil

PUC-PR

Jan 2016 — Dec 2018

Post-Graduate in Web Development, FURB

Brazil

Jan 2007 — Dec 2008

BSc in Information Technology, Uniasselvi

Brazil

Mar 2002 — Dec 2005